siteranklist.com 2015-10-20

# Privacy Policy - Site Rank List

_Last Updated: 1 June 2015. This Privacy Policy is only available in English._

siteranklist.com is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the way in which we gather, use, disclose and manage your data.

A. Acknowledgement and Acceptance of Terms  
B. Information we collect and how we use it  
C. Disclosing of Information  
D. Changes to this Privacy Policy

## A. Acknowledgement and Acceptance of Terms

By accessing any of our websites, you acknowledge that you fully understand this Privacy Policy and freely consent to the information collection and use practises described in this Privacy Policy.

## B. Information we collect and how we use it

We collect the following types of information:

### 1\. Information you provide

The information you provide when filling out any form on the website is stored. For example, when you search for a phrase, URL or domain, we need to process the request in order to provide our service to you. We may also retain the terms you searched for, in order to analyse the terms and to improve our service to you.

### 2\. User communication

When you send e-mail or other communication to us, we retain that information in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

### 3\. Cookies

When you visit our website, we may send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. A cookie is a small file of characters that allows a website to recognise your browser. Cookies cannot run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including storing user preferences to personalise or enhance your user experience.

### 4\. Log information

When you access our website, our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language and the date and time of your request.

### 5\. Third party applications

The website uses third party applications, such as Google Analytics, Google Adsense, the Facebook Like Button, the Twitter Tweet Button and the Google Plus One button, to improve the service we provide to you. Information may be collected by third party application providers and the collection thereof is governed by their privacy policies.

## C. Disclosing of Information

We may release information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to:

  * comply with the law,
  * enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or
  * protect the rights, property or safety of siteranklist.com, our users, or others.

## D. Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Our newest Privacy Policy is accessible at www.siteranklist.com/privacy.
